### Start typing and press enter to search

Search … 

Above Header

[

](https://toursgonewild.com/)

Main Menu

* [Destinations](https://toursgonewild.com/destinations/)Menu Toggle
* [Special Events](https://toursgonewild.com/special-events/)Menu Toggle
* GalleriesMenu Toggle
* About TGWMenu Toggle

* [Destinations](https://toursgonewild.com/destinations/)Menu Toggle
* [Special Events](https://toursgonewild.com/special-events/)Menu Toggle
* GalleriesMenu Toggle
* About TGWMenu Toggle

Above Header

[

](https://toursgonewild.com/)

Main Menu

* [Destinations](https://toursgonewild.com/destinations/)Menu Toggle
* [Special Events](https://toursgonewild.com/special-events/)Menu Toggle
* GalleriesMenu Toggle
* About TGWMenu Toggle

* [Destinations](https://toursgonewild.com/destinations/)Menu Toggle
* [Special Events](https://toursgonewild.com/special-events/)Menu Toggle
* GalleriesMenu Toggle
* About TGWMenu Toggle

* Where to Asia    Turkey    United Arab Emirates Central America    Costa Rica Europe    Croatia    Czech Republic    France    Germany    Greece    Hungary    Iceland    Italy    Netherlands    Portugal    Spain    Turkey    United Kingdom North America    Mexico    United States South America    Argentina    Brazil    Chile    Colombia    Peru    Uruguay
* Dates April August December February January July June March May November October September
* Ideal Length 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30
* Travel Style Adventure Bachelor Bachelorette Beach Celebrations City Escape Classic Explorer Festivals Group Luxury Nature Romantic Honeymoon Sport Trip Addons VIP Nightlife YOLO
* 

TGW Privacy Policy
==================

Last updated: August 12, 2020

This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.

We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Interpretation and Definitions**
==================================

**Interpretation**
------------------

The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.

The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.

**Definitions**
---------------

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:

* **You** means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.
* **Company** (referred to as either “the Company”, “We”,  “TGW”, “Us” or “Our” in this Agreement) refers to TGW Travel Group Inc, 6538 Collins Ave #370 Miami Beach, Fl 33141.
* **Affiliate** means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where “control” means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority.
* **Account** means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.
* **Website** refers to Tours Gone Wild, accessible from https://www.toursgonewild.com
* **Service** refers to the Website.
* **Country** refers to: Florida, United States
* **Service Provider** means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.
* **Third-party Social Media Service** refers to any website or any social network website through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.
* **Personal Data** is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
* **Cookies** are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device or any other device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that website among its many uses.
* **Device** means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.
* **Usage Data** refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

**Collecting and Using Your Personal Data**
===========================================

**Types of Data Collected**
---------------------------

### Personal Data

While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address
* First name and last name
* Phone number
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
* Usage Data

### Usage Data

Usage Data is collected automatically when using the Service.

Usage Data may include information such as Your Device’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

We may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device.

### Tracking Technologies and Cookies

We use Cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on Our Service and store certain information. Tracking technologies used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze Our Service.

You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies, You may not be able to use some parts of our Service.

Cookies can be “Persistent” or “Session” Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close your web browser.

We use both session and persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:

* **Necessary / Essential Cookies**

Type: Session Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies are essential to provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts. Without these Cookies, the services that You have asked for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You with those services.

* **Cookies Policy / Notice Acceptance Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies identify if users have accepted the use of cookies on the Website.

* **Functionality Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Us

Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences every time You use the Website.

* **Tracking and Performance Cookies**

Type: Persistent Cookies

Administered by: Third-Parties

Purpose: These Cookies are used to track information about traffic to the Website and how users use the Website. The information gathered via these Cookies may directly or indirectly identify you as an individual visitor. This is because the information collected is typically linked to a pseudonymous identifier associated with the device you use to access the Website. We may also use these Cookies to test new pages, features or new functionality of the Website to see how our users react to them.

For more information about the cookies we use and your choices regarding cookies, please visit our Cookies Policy.

**Use of Your Personal Data**
-----------------------------

The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes:

* **To provide and maintain our Service**, including to monitor the usage of our Service.
* **To manage Your Account:**to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user.
* **For the performance of a contract:**the development, compliance and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items or services You have purchased or of any other contract with Us through the Service.
* **To contact You:**To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application’s push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products or contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation.
* **To provide You**with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless You have opted not to receive such information.
* **To manage Your requests:**To attend and manage Your requests to Us.

We may share your personal information in the following situations:

* **With Service Providers:**We may share Your personal information with Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, to advertise on third party websites to You after You visited our Service, to contact You.
* **For Business transfers:**We may share or transfer Your personal information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
* **With Affiliates:**We may share Your information with Our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that We control or that are under common control with Us.
* **With Business partners:**We may share Your information with Our business partners to offer You certain products, services or promotions.
* **With other users:**when You share personal information or otherwise interact in the public areas with other users, such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside. If You interact with other users or register through a Third-Party Social Media Service, Your contacts on the Third-Party Social Media Service may see You name, profile, pictures and description of Your activity. Similarly, other users will be able to view descriptions of Your activity, communicate with You and view Your profile.

**Retention of Your Personal Data**
-----------------------------------

The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

**Transfer of Your Personal Data**
----------------------------------

Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at the Company’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of Your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from Your jurisdiction.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer.

The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and other personal information.

**Disclosure of Your Personal Data**
------------------------------------

### Business Transactions

If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, Your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before Your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

### Law enforcement

Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Other legal requirements

The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* Comply with a legal obligation
* Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company
* Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public
* Protect against legal liability

**Security of Your Personal Data**
----------------------------------

The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Detailed Information on the Processing of Your Personal Data**
================================================================

Service Providers have access to Your Personal Data only to perform their tasks on Our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Analytics**
-------------

We may use third-party Service providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

**Google Ads**

* Google Ads remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated)Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.
* For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

**Behavioral Remarketing**
--------------------------

The Company uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to You after You visited our Service. We and Our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on Your past visits to our Service.

* **AdRoll**

AdRoll remarketing service is provided by Semantic Sugar, Inc.

You can opt-out of AdRoll remarketing by visiting this AdRoll Advertising Preferences web page: [http://info.evidon.com/pub\_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false](http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false)

For more information on the privacy practices of AdRoll, please visit the AdRoll Privacy Policy web page: [http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)

**Children’s Privacy**
======================

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us. If We become aware that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from Our servers.

If We need to rely on consent as a legal basis for processing Your information and Your country requires consent from a parent, We may require Your parent’s consent before We collect and use that information.

**“Do not track” signals under California Online Privacy Protection Act (CALOPPA)**
===================================================================================

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

**Your data protection rights under (GDPR)** 
=============================================

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. TGW aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.**Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
* **The right of rectification.**You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
* **The right to object.**You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
* **The right of restriction.**You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
* **The right to data portability.**You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
* **The right to withdraw consent.**You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where  TGW Travel Group relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

**Legal basis for procesing personal data under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)** 

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), TGW Travel Group’s legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

TGW may process your Personal Data because:

* We need to perform a contract with you
* You have given us permission to do so
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights
* To comply with the law

**Electronic Communication**
============================

We collect email addresses of those users who have submitted their email addresses to our system. We do not resell or license or resell email addresses to any third party. Your email address will only be used for correspondence with you while booking your package with us or for marketing communications which you may opt out of.

**Information collected via our payment systems** 
==================================================

When making tour payments and deposits, we collect some personal information, depending on how the payment is made:

* Our card processors, Stripe, captures credit card payment information, and provides TGW with access to address information, as well as the last 4 digits only of the cardholder’s credit card number. This information is stored on the merchant services’ secure servers only, and is used for reference only. Credit card information is never added to the users file.  
* Paypal.com captures credit card and other payment information, and provides information of payment and amount only, as well as a reference number. No information of credit card numbers or address are made available.  

**Links to Other Websites**
===========================

Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**
==================================

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “Last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**
==============

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us:

* By email: [INFO@TOURSGONEWILD.COM](mailto:INFO@TOURSGONEWILD.COM)
* By Phone +1 786 522-3667

Get a Price Quote
-----------------

* Name\*
    
     First Last
    
* Email\*
    
* Phone
    
* No. of People
    
* Departure City
    
* More Details: (customization, desired experience, etc)
    
* 
* Comments
    
    This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

Δ

TGW Customer Reviews
--------------------

[

](https://www.ekomi-us.com/review-tgw-travel-group-inc.html "Customer review: Everything about our recent trip to Rio de Janeiro for New Years was incredible. TGW did an excellent job at setting up all of our accommodations and activities. Our guides were very attentive and quickly responded to any questions we had. The parties and dinners they set up for us were all amazing experiences, Im not sure if we wouldve been the same experience had we tried to seek out these things ourselves. They definitely made for an unforgettable experience and a great start to the year. I would definitely recommend them to anyone looking to travel to Rio or any of the other destinations they offer.")

Speak to a TGW Sales Rep
------------------------

###### **CALL US**

1-877-456-9453  
USA +1-786-522-3667  
UK +44 20 33719356  
BRAZIL +55 21 3549-4353

CALL US  
TOLL-FREE 1-877-456-9453  
USA +1-786-522-3667  
UK +44 20 33719356

**Get updates on our destinations, deals, giveaways & upcoming group trips**

Newsletter Sign-Up
------------------

### By

Get updates on our destinations, deals, giveaways & upcoming group trips

Enter your email address to subscribe. \*

Subscribe

ACCREDITED BY

THIRD-PARTY CUSTOMER REVIEWS

[

](https://www.ekomi-us.com/review-tgw-travel-group-inc.html)

FLORIDA SELLER OF TRAVEL NUMBER: ST35764

### Start typing and press enter to search

Search... 

Scroll to Top

We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.[Ok](#)
